Next time, we'll be playing the final
stage of Tsumotsumotsumono!
A new version of ourselves, HELLO
HELLO!
It doesn't matter what they say, it
doesn't matter what they do!
Let's attack them with passion, CHAO
CHAO!
Tsumotsumotsumono! The final stage!
The infinite possibilities, HELLO
HELLO!
Challenge everything you want to do!
Prove your exciting future!
Ah!
Happy New Day!
This program is a program where 6
people who are active to promote
something exciting
are challenged to do various things and
raise the excitement level in the world!
Let's challenge to do various things!
Tumor Tumor Tumorow!
The strongest!
Hello! Hello! to infinite
possibilities!
Challenge everything you want to do!
I'll prove the exciting future!
Happy New Day!
I'm a little strange.
I'll do my best!
You got another surprise!
2. Use your calculations
3. Choose the scenes you like
4. Take the time to watch it
Yes I do! You're quite heavy
Uh huh
Likependic
You'll come here
Ohh
Sh shaken Citiz.
Did it work out?
What a great shooting!
I'm glad I do 5 years filming with him.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching.
Good morning!
I'm shooting a music video now.
Shall I tell the picture now?
We just finished TV interview!
completed a new scene!
The first day of the MV shooting
Good morning!
It's my first time to shoot a MV, so
I'm a little nervous.
But I hope I can enjoy shooting!
I'll do my best!
I'm shooting now!
It's fun!
I'm just doing nothing.
Who's talking?
I can't hear anything.
I'm a newbie.
Let's go to the world of the strongest!
It's fun.
The weather is good.
Strawberry parfait!
It's delicious, cute and looks great.
I think I'll have strawberry parfait.
No, I'll have fruit parfait.
I'm not sure.
This is the first part of the music
video.
Which switch is the strongest?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back soon.
Where is your mother?
I'm crying.
I'm in trouble.
OK!
Is this OK?
Yes, it is.
OK, let's go to the cute one.
Kawari, let's laugh.
Kawari, please smile.
Want a kiss?
Tell me at the same time as you eat!
Player 3 receives the gold medal
Go to a winner
Urshaf
Where?
Masakadoool ran ADA
Ready, go!
I'm sorry.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Anpanman.
I don't know what you are talking
about.
What is this?
It's a vacuum cleaner.
I'm scared.
Ouch!
I'm
not
sure
.
I'm
not sure.
definitely
going to
go.
I'm
going to
go.
I'm
going to
go.
I'm
going to
I did it!
Thank you for watching.
Let's start the game.
Ready, go.
Let's go.
Thank you for watching!
My life, which I have to obey my school
uniform, didn't get any better...
Thank you.
Chokawaii! Chokawaii!
Julia Chokawaii! Chokawaii!
Isn't he wearing making-of clothes?
I'm going to be the strongest!
I don't care what people say
I'm going to take back what's mine
I'm going to be the strongest!
So cute!
Energetic!
More!
I like it!
I love it!
More!
This shooting was the first time since
I became a new member
It was the first time to shoot with 6
members including Aki
It was the first time to do something
like this
It was interesting
It was like 6 members were going to
beat Pabrin
Not Pabrin!
Pabrin!
More!
I'm going to be the strongest!
This music video is cute but there are
also some interesting scenes.
I think this music video has a lot of
interesting scenes.
The audience is amazed
Let's go!
Let's all work together
Let's dance with all our might
Shout out!
Seiki!
Makku!
Su!
Ai!
Makku!
Su!
Let's go.
Please turn it.
We've done a lot of music videos as
Tokimeki Senryuu, but this is our first
time as a super Tokimeki Senryuu.
I feel like we've finished a music
video that will make you even more
excited for the future.
We've done a lot of things that are
fun, cute, and full of various things.
We're going to help Pabrin, who is the
bad guy in the music video.
I hope you'll watch it.
Please watch it.
If you can hit it with all your might
and learn even one thing
You're honest!
Look at it with your long eyes, there's
no such thing as failure
It's just right to be laughed at
It's a good way to get ahead
You can't be careful when you're
heading for it
We can!
I want the strongest again
Oh no! Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow,
the strongest
Hello, hello to the wonderful world
It doesn't matter what the difficult
story is
Just being alive is exciting
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow, the
strongest
Hello, hello to the unexpected meeting
For now, let's live with a smile
Thank you, water and sweet flowers